soundcircuit.com 2014-06-17

# None

**Warning** : include(contact/head.inc) [function.include]: failed to open stream: No such file or directory in **/home/admin/domains/soundcircuit.com/public_html/about/privacy.php** on line **1**

**Warning** : include() [function.include]: Failed opening 'contact/head.inc' for inclusion (include_path='.:/usr/local/lib/php') in **/home/admin/domains/soundcircuit.com/public_html/about/privacy.php** on line **1**

## Privacy Statement

SoundCircuit.com values your privacy. To keep you informed, we've created this privacy statement that discloses our intent and methods for online use of information.   

SoundCircuit.com requires a valid e-mail address for users who want to participate in the forum. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should any questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile. 

Also in the forum registration, you have the option of providing some additional information such as college, occupation, homepage, picture, and interests. This information is made available to other users to create a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed. 

Please remember that anything that is disclosed on the forum becomes public, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our forum. Your computer's IP address will not be visible to the regular users of the site. 

Cookies are pieces of information that a site transfers to your hard disk for record-keeping. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. 

Certain activities on the Circuit Board involve the use of "cookies" to facilitate your experience. This includes retention of your username and password for, and showing a default Topic View. You have the option to turn these cookies off at any time by updating your user profile preferences. If your browser doesnâ€™t support cookies, or if you have cookies turned off, these preferences will not be set. 

SoundCircuit.com does not disclose your personally identifying information to any third parties for any purpose. All reasonable care is taken to ensure its security both offline and online. It is our policy to destroy server access to personal information provided. 

**Important:** Itâ€™s also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number, or picture) in a post on the forum, or privately to a member of the forum, that information is publicly available and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage the offering of any personally identifying information within the message board itself, and to members via chat, instant message, e-mails, etc. 

If you would like to update your profile on SoundCircuit.com, just click **Edit Profile** at any time, and modify your information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [**click here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us. 

**Warning** : include(contact/foot.inc) [function.include]: failed to open stream: No such file or directory in **/home/admin/domains/soundcircuit.com/public_html/about/privacy.php** on line **36**

**Warning** : include() [function.include]: Failed opening 'contact/foot.inc' for inclusion (include_path='.:/usr/local/lib/php') in **/home/admin/domains/soundcircuit.com/public_html/about/privacy.php** on line **36**
